>> Kyle Simpson: 现在我不仅保证了更清洁的代码样式，而且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now I promised
not only a cleaner code style, but
更强大的设计模式
a more powerful design pattern.
委派是设计模式，设计模式应该影响，
Delegation is a design pattern,
and design patterns should affect,
他们应该改变你对设计代码的看法
they should change the way that
you think about designing a code.
所以在我们最后的讨论中我想谈谈
And so, in this last part of our
discussion, I want to talk about
应如何以不同的方式解决代表团的问题，
how delegation should be approached
to solve problems differently,
不仅仅是用不同的方式编写代码，而是从根本上解决了问题。
not just to write code differently, but to
solve problems fundamentally differently.
想象一下你有这样的情景。
Imagine you have a scenario like this.
假设您具有需要在应用程序中构造的登录页面
Imagine you have a login page that you
need to construct in your application and
你会有两个不同的控制器
you're going to have two
different controllers.
您将有一个代表认证部分的 AuthController ，
You're gonna have an AuthController
that represents the authentication part,
例如与服务器通信。
like communicating with the server.
你会有一个代表所有人的 LoginFormController
And you're gonna have a
LoginFormController, which represents all
UI 内容，文本框，按钮和错误消息，以及所有这些信息。
the UI stuff, the text boxes, and buttons,
and error messages, and all of that, okay.
设计这个的旧的学校方式是你需要两套行为
The old school way of designing this is
that you need both sets of behaviors in
某种形式的形态和形式你需要它们都组成
some way, shape or form,
you need them both composed,
或者你需要他们俩的权限
or you need access to both of them.
原来的学校方式
So the old school way,
这就是我们典型的 Java类继承系统
which is what we would typically think of
in a class inheritance system like Java,
是您将其中一个作为父类，另一个为子类。
is you make one of them the parent class,
the other one the child class.
然后您将实例化以获取此 pageInstance。
And then you instantiate
to get this pageInstance.
它有来自 AuthController 的所有方法以及来自
And it has all the methods from
AuthController and all the methods from
此实例中存在 LoginFormController 。
the LoginFormController
present in this instance.
然后你就可以为所欲为了
And then you can do whatever
you need to do for the page.
这就是如何解决这个问题的
That's sort of how the inheritance
way of solving this
问题就会被解决
problem would have approached it.
这就是我们所谓的构图遗传。
That's what we called
composition thru inheritance.
20 世纪 80 年代和 1990年的愿景是如何构建软件。
This was the 1980's and 1990's vision for
how software should be built.
在 90 年代中期到 90 年代中期你开始听说
Somewhere in the mid to late 90s,
you started to hear that this whole
15 层深的继承链就像一个反模式
15-level deep inheritance chain
thing was like an anti-pattern.
人们开始说，不，不，不，我们不想做
And people started saying, no, no,
no, we don't wanna do composition thru
继承，我们要做的是组成，而不是继承的组成。
inheritance, we wanna do composition
instead over composition over inheritance.
除去所有垂直定向的嵌套链和
Get rid of all those
vertically-oriented nested chains and
让我们把这些东西一起组合起来
let's just have these things
compose themselves together.
所以组成他们的一种方式就是要有这两门课，
So one way of composing them
is to have these two classes,
把其中一个实例化，然后当您实例化另一个时，
to instantiate one of them, and
then when you instantiate the other one,
让它成为第一个的财产
make it a property of the first one.
所以现在我可以访问 pageInstance 和 pageInstance 上的所有方法
So now I have access to all
the methods on pageInstance and
所有 offInstance 的方法都是在一个地方进行的，它们是一起组成的。
all the methods on offInstance all in
one place, they are composed together.
这是一种合成方法。
That's one way of doing that composition.
然后有人说，好吧，这很丑，因为如果我需要创作更多的
And then somebody said, well, that's ugly
because then if I need to compose more I
都有这些属性让我们做个混混
got all these properties, let's do mixins.
然后我们发明了混合组合的概念。
So then we invented the idea of
mixin composition, which said,
我将实例化一个 ControllerClass 并实例化 AuthControllerClass。
I'm gonna instantiate a ControllerClass
and instantiate an AuthControllerClass.
然后我就把所有东西都复制到另一个
And then I'm just gonna copy
everything over into the other one.
所以现在所有这些方法都被复制了。
So now all those methods
have been copied over.
所有这些都是我们解决这个问题的方法
All of these are different ways
that we've solved the problem,
我想把这两个逻辑分开
which is I want to logically
separate these two things.
但他们需要让我共存，才能让页面工作。
But then they need to coexist for
me to actually get the page to work.
我的意思是，他们需要以某种方式组成。
By coexist I mean,
they need to be composed in some way.
我们一直试图发明不同的方法来创作这些东西。
And we've been trying to invent
different ways to compose this things.
那么，代表团的答案是什么呢 ?
So, what is delegation's answer to this?
代表团如何以不同的方式做 ?
How does delegation do things differently?
第一，你对代表团做的事，不好意思。
Number one, the thing that you
do with delegation, excuse me.
你对代表团所做的事情就是停止思考父母和
The thing that you do with delegation
is you stop thinking about parent and
然后开始考虑同级之间的关系。
child and
you start thinking about peer-to-peer.
因此，我可以有一个链接到 AuthController的 LoginFormController 。
So I could have a LoginFormController
that is linked to an AuthController.
我们得摆脱这个父母孩子的想法
We have to get rid of this
idea of a parent-child and
请考虑同级之间的情况。
think about the peer-to-peer.
我们会说 LoginController 链接到 AuthController好吗
We're gonna just say LoginController
is linked to AuthController, all right?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一个在 JavaScript中使用的代码示例。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So here's an example
in code of doing that in JavaScript.
我要制作一个有认证和认证方法的 AuthController
I'm gonna make an AuthController that
has methods on it like authenticate and
handleResponse。
handleResponse.
然后我要去做一个 LoginFormController
And then I'm gonna make a
LoginFormController, and it has methods on
它类似于表单的 onSubmit 处理程序和 displayError 消息。
it like an onSubmit handler for
the form and a displayError message.
并且 LoginFormController 链接到，通过原型链，
And LoginFormController is linked to,
through the prototype chain,
授权控制器。
the AuthController.
但这些是两个不同的具体物体。
But these are two separate
concrete objects.
不像他们是一个阶级
It's not like they're a class for
这些东西实际上是两个独立的物体。
these things,
they are actual two separate objects.
如果你需要的话，你可以单独与他们互动。
And you could interact with them
separately if you needed to.
但是部分时间，他们需要彼此合作。
But part of the time,
they need to cooperate with each other.
例如，每当我要 onSubmit 时，就像你在这里看到的一样，
So for example, whenever I got
to onSubmit, as you see here,
每当我转至 onSubmit 时，我需要在第 18 行上调用 this.authenticate 。
whenever I go to onSubmit, I need to
call this.authenticate on line 18.
但 LoginFormController 没有认证方法。
But the LoginFormController doesn't
have an authenticate method.
因此，将方法委派给 AuthControl 对象。
And so that method is delegated
to the AuthControl object.
因此，我们运行认证方法，但是
So we then run the authenticate method,
but
我们要指出的关键是什么
what is the this key we're gonna point at?
还会指向 LoginFormController 的位置，对吧 ?
It's still gonna be pointing
at LoginFormController, right?
所以我们真正做到的是
So what we have actually done is through
这个关键词在原型系统中的独角兽魔法
the unicorn magic of the this key
word in the prototype system,
在函数调用过程中，我们实际上组成了这两个对象。
we have virtually composed these two
objects during the function call.
它们现在在此关键字上的共享上下文中
They are now in a shared context
over the this keyword where
这两个人可以彼此交谈，彼此分享。
both of them can talk to each other and
share with each other.
我们在此调用认证方法。
Here we are calling
the authenticate method.
但是当在第 4 行上认证为 this.userName 时，
But when authenticate says
this.userName on line 4,
它实际上是指在 LoginFormController上返回的用户名属性。
it's actually referring to the username
property back on LoginFormController.
因此，它能够访问这些属性并在需要时使用它们。
So it's able to access those properties
and use them as it needs them.
然后，每当 handleResponse 从服务器返回并出现错误时，
And then whenever the handleResponse comes
back from the server and there's an error,
在第 9 行我知道现在有很多箭头但在我们说的第 9 行
on line 9, I know there is a lot of
arrows now, but on line 9 when we say,
this.displayError，我们没有 displayError，但是 who do?
this.displayError, we don't have
a displayError, but who does?
LoginFormController。
The LoginFormController.
你看这两个单独的具体物体是如何
So you see how these two separate
concrete objects have virtually
在共享的上下文中相互组合吗 ?
composed each other over
the shared this context?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是一个非常不同的想法
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's a very
different way of thinking about how we
解决软件问题。
solve software.
我们解决软件
We solve software,
我们有两个单独的具体事情可以做他们自己的工作
we have two separate concrete
things that can do their own work.
但是合作的时候，合作的方式是没有实例的
But when they need to cooperate, the way
they cooperate is not having instance
call instance a call instance.b 方法。
a call instance a call instance.b method.
他们合作的方式是通过原型链联系起来的
The way they cooperate is linked
through the prototype chain,
他们只会分享一个电话背景
they just share a call context.
他们可以根据需要调用对方的方法。
And they can call each
other's methods as necessary.
>> Kyle Simpson: 该方法的诸多好处之一是如果
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: One of the many
benefits of that approach is that if
您有单独的对象仅通过原型链进行链接，
you have separate objects that are only
linked through a prototype chain,
因为这些物体是分开的而不是通过连接在一起
because those objects are separate
instead of being wired together through
类层次结构或任何事物，它们变得更加稳定。
class hierarchies or anything,
they become much more testable.
稳定可靠。
Independently testable.
所以说我有这两个物体
So lets say I have these two objects and
我想做的是做一个我可以测试的模拟
what I want to do is I want to make
a mock that I can test against.
所以，让我们来模拟作者。
So let's mock out the AuthController.
我正在通过嘲弄 AuthController 来测试 LoginFormController 。
I'm testing the LoginFormController
by mocking the AuthController.
我只需要将 LoginFormController 原型链接到
All I have to do is have the
LoginFormController prototype linked to
我的模拟对象
my mock object.
我不需要更改代码的任何内容。
I didn't have to change
anything about the code.
我只是改变了它的雏形
I just change where its prototype linked.
你可以用 proto 做这个记得吗
You can do that with a proto, remember?
因此，我现在正在通过嘲弄 AuthController 来测试 LoginFormController ，但
So now I'm testing the LoginFormController
by mocking out the AuthController, but
如果我想测试另一个呢
what if I wanna test the other one?
如果我想测试 AuthController 呢 ?
What if I wanna test the AuthController?
我做了一个 MockLoginFormController 的代表
Well, I make a MockLoginFormController
that delegates to
授权控制器现在我正在测试授权控制器
the AuthController, and
now I'm testing the AuthController.
我可以完全独立设置这些测试。
I can set up these tests
entirely independent.
我不需要测试依赖性注入或任何其他无稽之谈。
I don't need test dependency injection or
any of that other nonsense.
这些测试完全独立于代码
These tests are just entirely
separate of the code,
他们只会改变原型机链的关联
they just change where the prototype
chain linkage happens.
我们可以模拟出不同的物体
And we're able to mock out
the different objects.
如果你有三，四，四，
And that gets even more powerful
if you have three or four or
在原型链中的五个对象。
five objects that are in
the prototype chain.
您可以模拟不同的部件来隔离和测试。
You can mock out different
parts to isolate and test.
>> Kyle Simpson: 那就是我的案子
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So that's my case for
为什么我觉得我们已经错过了班上的课
why I think we've been missing
the mark by doing classes.
我明白为什么有时甚至连一个选项都没有
I understand why there is
sometimes not even an option,
这个框架为你做出了选择
the framework makes the choice for you.
就算你有选择权
Or even if you do have an option,
我知道有时候会有情感上的依恋
I understand sometimes that there's
an emotional attachment to doing classes.
我有那么多东西
I get all of that stuff.
但我真的认为如果你认真地理解和理解
But I really think that if you
are taking seriously, understanding and
学习 JavaScript 这个努力的一部分是
learning JavaScript,
part of that endeavor is,
如何以最有效的方式使用 JavaScript ?
how do I use JavaScript in its
most effectively designed way?
我也不觉得他们在课堂上都有这么多糖分
And I don't think even with all the sugar
they've layered on top of classes
能满足 JavaScript DNA 的标记
that it meets the mark of
the DNA of JavaScript.
这就是 JavaScript 的本质。
That's what JavaScript does inherently.
JavaScript 执行的操作和
What JavaScript does and
它本身就是一个代表团，它是一个原型代表团。
does well inherently is delegation,
it does prototype delegation.
我想知道的是，我希望看到更多的人拥抱这一点。
And what I'd like to see is, I'd like
to see more people embracing that.
然后去寻找更多的复杂
And going after that rather than
trying to find more complex
在类语法上层的方式。
ways to layer on class syntax.